=== SECTION BOUNDARIES (Heading 1) ===

Para   30: DECLARATION OF ORIGINALITY
Para   41: ABSTRACT
Para   45: ÍZET
Para   57: DEDICATION
Para   69: ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS
Para   75: TABLE OF CONTENTS
Para  257: LIST OF FIGURES
Para  263: LIST OF TABLES
Para  270: LIST OF ABBREVIATIONS
Para  291: INTRODUCTION
Para  410: DATASET ANALYSIS AND DATA PIPELINE
Para  551: Stage 1: RCT Detection with YOLOv11x
Para  694: Preprocessing Experiments: The Quest for Optimal Enhancement
Para  863: Dataset Generation Strategies: From Manual to Automatic Labeling
Para 1039: Stage 2: Model Architecture Evolution and Selection
Para 1170: CLASS IMBALANCE SOLUTIONS
Para 1217: Pipeline Optimization Journey: From Research to Clinical System
Para 1367: Final System Architecture
Para 1592: Results and Discussion
Para 1920: Conclusion and Future Work
